fallon.com 2009-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Skimmer - We Are Fallon

### Skimmer Privacy Policy

This privacy policy ("Policy") describes the information Fallon Group, Inc. d/b/a Fallon Worldwide may collect, how we may collect and use it, with whom we may share it, and certain other privacy issues, including the precautions we take to protect your privacy.

Before submitting information, please read this Policy. Download and/or use of the Skimmer Application indicates your acceptance of this Policy and agreement to the collection and use of your personal information in accordance with the Policy. 

**Please Note:** This Policy applies only to personally identifiable information collected directly by the Skimmer Application. The specific privacy policies for each of the services to which the Skimmer Application allows you to link (i.e., Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Flickr and Blogger (collectively, the “Services”)) still apply to any personally identifiable information collected directly through those Services. This Policy also does not apply to information collected or obtained by Fallon Worldwide or its partners through other means. Fallon Worldwide is not in any way associated or affiliated with the providers of the Services and the Skimmer Application has not been reviewed, approved or endorsed by the providers of the Services.

#### Types of information that may be collected

The following are the types of information we may collect:

**Information You Provide Us:** Personal information you provide us may include an e-mail address, user name, avatar (if applicable) and password, as well as the user name and password for each of the Services. 

**Skimmer Application Usage Information:** We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you use the Skimmer Application. For example, we may collect click-stream data and your IP address. 

**Information from Other Sources:** We may add information from other sources to your personal information, but shall only use the resulting information in connection with the Skimmer Application. 

**Other Materials Stored:** The Skimmer Application will cache the following information: 

  * Twitter: statuses, @tweets, direct messages
  * Flickr: photos info: farm_id, server_id, secret, photo url, contacts info: user name, real name
  * Facebook: status updates which include birthday and profile, photo tag and album url, friends name
  * Blogger: posted content
  * Youtube: link to uploaded video

#### How information may be collected

We may collect information from you in different areas on the Skimmer Application, including but not limited to those described below:

**Registration**

To use the Skimmer Application, you will be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information, including an e-mail address and password. In order to establish a connection with each Service, with which you wish to connect using the Skimmer Application, you will also be required to complete an authentication process for each Service which may include providing your user name and password for the applicable Service. 

**Cookies**

The Skimmer Application uses standard technology called "cookies," which are small data files transferred to your computer when you allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your Web browser to the Skimmer Application whenever you initiate the Skimmer Application, and make the Skimmer Application easier to use by saving your passwords and preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Skimmer Application, cookies help us determine which elements are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Skimmer Application are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Skimmer Application. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you generally can opt out of providing this information by turning the cookies off in your browser; however, some areas of the Skimmer Application may not provide you with a personalized experience if you disable the use of cookies.

We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information. An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. Our computers identify your computer by its IP address. When you request Web pages from the Skimmer Application, our computers log your IP address. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from the Skimmer Application. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. This data helps us understand how individuals use the Skimmer Application. 

#### How we use the collected information

Personally identifiable information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties. We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Skimmer Application. We do this to offer more targeted services to you and to customize and enhance your use of the Skimmer Application. We will not provide individual data but will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. 

In addition, we reserve the right to contact a user regarding account status, changes to this Policy, the Terms of Use and other matters that relate to the underlying service and/or the information collected. 

#### With whom the information may be shared

At times, we may share your personally identifiable information with others for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others: 

**Agents** : We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include application maintenance, data analysis and customer service. These entities only access the personally identifiable information to perform their functions, but may not use the information for other purposes. 

**Aggregate Information:** We may share aggregate information such as demographics and Skimmer Application usage statistics with other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information. 

**Partners Subsidiaries and Affiliates:** We may share your information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) with subsidiaries and affiliates of Fallon Worldwide for the purpose of managing or performing duties and functions relating to the Skimmer Application, and any such subsidiaries and affiliates would use your information only as permitted under this Privacy Policy.

**Business Transfers:** Fallon Worldwide or the Skimmer Application may be sold along with its assets, or other transactions may occur in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred. In such a case, your personally identifiable information, which we have gathered, may be one of the business assets transferred. 

**Legal Process:** In the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process, your personally identifiable information may be disclosed pursuant to such subpoena, court order or legal process, which may be without notice to you. 

#### Links to Other Web Sites

This Policy applies only to the Skimmer Application. When you use the Skimmer Application and click on an item displayed in your feed, you will be taken to the Web site of the applicable Service that corresponds with that feed, which is beyond our control. For example, if you click on a status update in your feed from Facebook, you will be taken to the Facebook page. Similarly, if you click on a photo from your Flickr account, you will be taken to the appropriate page on Flickr. The Service Web sites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information. If you visit a Web site that is linked to our Skimmer Application, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information. 

#### Security

This Skimmer Application incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect, and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration, such as Secure Sockets Layer or "SSL" and firewalls, to ensure that your information is secure and confidential. Certain personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information to carry out business functions are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required. The Skimmer Application requires a password. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. It is important to recognize that whatever you transmit or disclose online could be collected and used by others or unlawfully intercepted by third parties. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

#### Children Under 13

The Skimmer Application is not intended for use by children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

#### Notification of changes and your acceptance of the policy

By using this Skimmer Application, you agree to the terms of this Policy. All modifications or updates will be posted to the Skimmer Application. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by e-mail or some other means. Your continued use of the Skimmer Application constitutes your acceptance of such revised privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use our site. 

#### Correction/Updating/Removal of Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information (such as your e-mail address) changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Skimmer Application, you may correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us by making changes to your profile or by e-mailing us at skimmer@fallon.com. If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, you can contact us at skimmer@fallon.com.
